So, Jostra-san, you don't know
where Jotaro is right now?
I can't feel his presence at all.
Polnareff and Iggy, I hope they're safe.
So then, do you think...
Even if we're the only ones left
standing, we've got to defeat Dio.
Kakyoin, how are your eyes?
Yes, I'm doing much better now.
Sorry for the trouble I put you through.
But I'm ready now to fight Dio to
the fullest extent of my power.
Be vigilant, Kakyoin.
Even Avdol was taken out
in the blink of an eye.
Even though we encountered
Dio's stand, the world,
we weren't able to actually
see its abilities at all.
There has to be something.
Some way to fight Dio.
Dio is after us.
Yes, he'll be coming after my
Joestar blood, that's for certain.
He plans to finish us before sunrise.
Before then, we're sure to get a chance
to uncover the secret of his stand.
And once we do, then we strike.
I don't know.
These automobiles, what power and speed.
Back when I was born, there were
only horse carriages around.
Ah, this really sucks.
Is this car still working?
And just who the hell are you?
You?
You didn't get hurt?
I'm asking you if this
car is still working?
Hey hold on if you're not
hurt then just get lost!
And another thing keep your damn
hands off the car buddy or maybe
you bumped into it On purpose
knowing that it's the senator's car?
Oh, you young people seem to
act on your impulses too easily.
Well, in any case, I apologize
for my driver's behavior.
And I hope you didn't get hurt.
Start the car.
We can't.
You knocked out my driver.
Well, if you're in a hurry,
and I don't mean to offend you,
please take this and you can hail a taxi.
Shut up and drive.
What in God's name do
you think you're doing?
Do you have any idea
who you're dealing with?
It's the small red pickup truck ahead.
Drive until you catch up.
Huh?
You're crazy.
You can't imagine you're actually
going to get away with this.
I'm a center of the United
States of America, goddammit!
If we don't catch up, you're dead.
You're insane!
I'll execute you!
I'll have you executed for this!
What the hell?!
Hurry up and start the car.
Somebody help me!
You'd better hurry up,
while you're still alive.
Tch, must have broke a few of them.
But I'm lucky to be alive,
even though I have no idea how I managed
to survive Dio's point-blank attack.
Just what is his stand, anyway?
I've heard the tarot card
representing it is the world.
I couldn't even see his
stand, let alone study it.
But I did figure out one thing.
Dio.
I hate to admit it,
but the speed and power
of your stand and my
Star Platinum look to be
pretty evenly matched.
Still, there's something else.
Some kind of incredible secret.
He's way more intimidating than any
of the other stand users I've met.
It's no wonder N'Doul and Iced
pledge their undying loyalty to Dio.
I guess you're bad-assed enough
to be my opponent, all right.
Hurry it up.
If you just take a look around,
I'm sure you'll understand
that the traffic is very bad.
It's not moving at all.
There's some space on the sidewalk.
You can't be serious.
What about my reputation?
The sidewalk is packed with people.
It doesn't matter. Go.
You need to go faster.
Yes, sir.
Faster.
Dio, please stop this.
I don't think so.
He's coming, Kakyoin.
Dio, the dark atmosphere he
exudes is closing in on us.
But where is he?
Hmm, I can feel his existence through the
sensations in the Joestar blood we share.
I know he's nearby, but I
can't pinpoint his location.
Fortunately, the same goes for him.
Kakyoin, take a look around.
If we have to fight him here, we'll
involve a lot of innocent people.
Hmm?
What is it?
Something's going on.
What? Team.
A red pickup, a red pickup.
I'll bet that's the one
you were talking about.
I'll make sure he doesn't get away.
Pull up a little bit closer.
The game is almost over, Joseph.
It's Kakyoin's Hierophant.
He evaded Emerald Splash
at such close range?
All right, then.
Shit, didn't even graze him.
I'll concentrate it more this time.
Don't get too close to him.
Kakyoin, retreat for now.
We can't fight without a strategy.
I'll just try to lose him.
But Chostar-san, we haven't figured
out anything about his stand.
No!
Kakyoin!
Back off!
Retreat!
Kakyoin! Behind you!
I don't know.
We bought ourselves some
time to work on a strategy.
Kakyoin, how are your wounds?
I'm sorry.
I lost control of myself.
But I was able to figure out
a couple things. About Dio?
The world is similar to
Jotaro's Star Platinum.
It doesn't seem to possess
any projectile weapons,
and its reach appears to
be relatively limited.
I think that could work to our advantage.
We get beaten before we even
realize what's going on. Why?
For us not to sense his
presence when he appears.
Suddenly appearing like that?
What kind of secret power could that be?
Is it possible for his stand to possess
some sort of teleportation abilities?
If so, that would explain
why he's able to...
Kakyoin, that's not like you.
A hasty conclusion could
cost you your life.
You can't be too careful when dealing
with someone as powerful as Dio.
Hm?
What the...?
Kakyoin!
Dio!
How can he involve
innocent people in this?
Is something the matter, Kakyoin? Huh?
I have an idea.
A way to reveal the true
nature of Dio's stand.
Hmm, there's no use trying.
Hmm, I don't see Kakyoin around.
Are they going to attack from two sides?
Damn, it's Kakyoin's Hierophant!
A barrier created by Hierophant!
How clever of you!
What is this?
There you go, Dio.
How do you like my barrier?
The Hierophant's barrier
fires back when touched.
Surrounds you in a radius of 20 meters.
I can detect every single
move that you make.
Same goes for your stand.
We've got you now, Dio.
Show it to us.
The world's secret.
Kakyoin, your first name
is Noriyaki, isn't it?
How old are you now? What?
Why would someone so young
wish to hurry his death?
I'm afraid you don't understand the severity
of the situation you're in now, Dio.
No matter what kind of
power the world possesses,
you cannot move one inch from that spot.
Do you really believe that?
Try it, then.
Are you frightened of
me, Noriyaki Kakyoin?
Just like you were last year. No way!
Yes, it's true that I gave in to
nauseating fear when I first met you.
But no longer!
Kakyoin, you are a thoughtful
and excellent stand user.
Such unusual qualities?
What worth do you see in protecting and
sacrificing your life for
an old man like Joseph?
While Jotaro and Joseph-san did save me.
That's only part of the
reason I fight with them now!
I've been fighting to regain my honor after
all the indignities I suffered from you.
It is not too late yet!
Pledge eternal loyalty and you will live.
Here is my answer?
Deal!
You fool!
Very well.
Witness now my stand, which has the
power to rule this world completely.
The world!
My stand is the world, you see.
Although,
in the stillness of time, you are not
able to see nor feel anything at all.
Die, Kakyoin!
You don't even know that
your death is now assured.
There's no way for you
to know what happened.
You're next, old man.
At last, Joseph.
Just you and me now.
Dio.
What happened?
Did Dio do this? But...
I can't move.
Is it seven o 'clock now?
Must be midnight in Japan.
Father. Mother.
I'm sorry.
It seems my time is running out.
This has been a short life.
But thanks to Jotaro and the others,
I can die knowing that I
didn't give in to my fear.
Although I was no match for Dio's
power, I lived my life as I wanted.
I have no regrets but one.
Joestar-san, I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to defeat Dio, nor
find the secrets to Dio's stand.
but why why was a perfect barrier broken
all at once i saw
every move despite that
not just one part but
the entire barrier of
20 meters at once why without any time lag
without any time lag
time
that must be it it's the
only thing I can think
of time he can stop time
I must let him know this
shocking truth somehow I
must let Jostar-san know
otherwise Jostar-san's And
Holly-san's lives will be...
Don't you agree, Joseph?
The best way to melt my
head onto Jonathan Joestar's
body is to use the blood
of his closest relative.
Joseph Joestar, I'm letting you know that
I will kill you by sucking your blood.
Before it adapts, I'll cut you in
half right through that scar of yours!
That bloodline of yours that speaks
too boldly is now coming to an end.
Now you die!
Last...
He's shooting in such a random direction.
It could well be the
exertion of his last moments.
That can't be.
Kakyoin is not the kind of man to do
something pointless at a time like this.
But why that clock tower?
Message from me.
This is all I can do.
Joestar-san, please, accept it.
Kakyoin!
Dio!
Take this!
You old man, your stand is
the most pathetic of them all!
There must be some
important meaning to it.
Kakyoin, what was it you tried
to tell me with the clock tower?
Destroying the clock tower like
that, what's the meaning of it all?
It's no use trying to escape, Joseph.
Could it be Dio's The World Secret?
But to destroy the clock!
To stop the clock!
Ha!
Stopping the clock!
Impossible.
He's saying the world can stop time?
I understand now, Kakyoin.
The message you sent me with your last
ounce of strength, I have received it.
What?
Hmph, you are quite a
schemer, aren't you, Joseph?
The same could be said about you.
So, you noticed my wave
energy shield, huh?
Well, I know something about you, too.
For you to come after
us like this must mean
that your ability to stop
time is very limited.
Isn't that right, Dio?
Well, you managed to figure it out.
I have to compliment you on that.
The one to figure it out was Kakyoin.
He did not die in vain.
So you figured it out.
Big deal.
There's nothing you're going
to be able to do about it.
Your wave energy means nothing to me.
Jotaro, stay back!
Don't come near me!
It's Jotaro.
Just as I suspected, he's still alive.
But he is out of the range of my stand.
I'll deal with Joseph first.
Jotaro, the true nature
of the world is time.
Dio's stand can stop time.
In the beginning, my power was only
able to stop time for a split second.
But as the scar on my neck is fading,
the time frame has increased
up to five seconds.
Soon, I will be able to stop
time for as long as I may desire.
Guarding yourself with wave energy
won't do you any good, Joseph.
A hundred years ago, the wave
energy was a slight problem for me.
But now with the power of the
world, it's insignificant.
Jonathan's grandson Joseph.
Your life has come to an end.
Three seconds. Two.
One. Zero.
Old man...
Jotaro!
Don't go near him.
Keep your distance.
You're no match for him.
I've already finished
off your friend, Kakyoin.
Jotaro, you're the last one.
You bastard, Dio.
Oh, are you coming for me?
You're not obeying your late grandfather.
You're coming very close to Dio.
Yeah, gotta get closer.
to mess you up.
Vincere
Vincere Vincere
And I love you in the shadow?
Thank you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.